Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/maria-butler-rn-bsn-ccrn-2947b3185 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Nursing

PIV

Phlebotomy

Certifications

CPR & AED

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Pediatric) (CCRN-P)

Maria Butler RN, BSN, CCRN

Nursing Manager Off-Shift Operations at Cambridge Hospital/ Nursing Administration

Greater Boston Area

Summary

I have 30 years of clinical and leadership experience. I have one year of management. I have worked with a very diverse patient population. I worked 20 years in a pediatric ICU. That offered me a lot of specialty learning opportunities.

Experience

CHA Cambridge Health Alliance
Nursing Manager
February 2020 - Present (5 months)
Cambridge, Massachusetts/Cambridge Hospital

Off-Shift Operations Manager/Nursing Administration

Boston Children's Hospital Clinical Coordinator/Registered Nurse March 1999 - April 2019 (20 years 2 months) Boston, Massachusetts

Clinical Coordinator Blood Donor Center May 2018-April 2019, Pediatric Medical/Surgical ICU March 1999-May 2018.

Boston Regional Medical Center Charge Nurse August 1989 - February 1999 (9 years 7 months) Stoneham, Massachusetts

I worked on a combination unit which was comprised of Adult Medical/Surgical and Pediatric patients.

Education

Salem State University

Bachelor of science in nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse